(Spock(on screen):)Because she feels. I don't.
(Spock(on screen):)All I know is logic.
(scoffs):
Yeah, right.
(turns off TV)
(Sheldon:)You can just shut
your feelings off.
(Sheldon:)There goes television,
lying to us again.
(Sheldon:)We let you
(Sheldon:)raise our children,
(Sheldon:)and this is the thanks we get.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, how could I
have been so foolish
(Sheldon:)to try and follow
in the footsteps
(Sheldon:)of a made-up alien race
with no emotions?
(sighs):
Well...
(Leonard:)now instead of idolizing
fictional characters,
(Leonard:)you can focus on the real people
who are already in your life.
(Sheldon:)Those are very wise words.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)They'd just be
so much more comforting
(Sheldon:)if they came
out of a television.